18 minutes is an absolutely brutal time limit,
18 λεπτά είναι ένα απόλυτα σκληρό χρονικό όριο
so I'm going to dive straight in, right at the point
γι' αυτό θα μπω κατευθείαν στο θέμα, ακριβώς στο σημείο
where I get this thing to work.
όπου θα το εξηγήσω.
Here we go. I'm going to talk about five different things.
Πάμε λοιπόν. Θα μιλήσω για πέντε διαφορετικά πράγματα.
I'm going to talk about why defeating aging is desirable.
Θα μιλήσω για το γιατί το να νικήσουμε τη γήρανση είναι επιθυμητό.
I'm going to talk about why we have to get our shit together,
Θα μιλήσω για το γιατί πρέπει να βάλουμε το μπάχαλό μας σε τάξη
and actually talk about this a bit more than we do.
και στην πραγματικότητα θα μιλήσω γι' αυτό λίγο περισσότερο από όσο μιλάμε γενικά.
I'm going to talk about feasibility as well, of course.
Θα μιλήσω επίσης, φυσικά, για τη δυνατότητα επίτευξης.
I'm going to talk about why we are so fatalistic
Θα μιλήσω για το γιατί είμαστε τόσο μοιρολατρικοί
about doing anything about aging.
σχετικά με οτιδήποτε σχετίζεται με τη γήρανση.
And then I'm going spend perhaps the second half of the talk
Και μετά θα ξοδέψω ίσως το δεύτερο μισό της ομιλίας
talking about, you know, how we might actually be able to prove that fatalism is wrong,
μιλώντας για το πώς θα μπορούσαμε να αποδείξουμε ότι η μοιρολατρία αυτή είναι λάθος,
namely, by actually doing something about it.
συγκεκριμένα, με το να κάνουμε κάτι για αυτή.
I'm going to do that in two steps.
Θα το κάνω αυτό σε δύο βήματα.